你好
Hi. Hello.
早上好 西沃恩
Good morning, Siobhan.
很抱歉今天打扰您
Sorry to bother you today
早上好 莎伦 没关系的
Uh, hey. Sharon. Uh, hi. No problem.
我本想跟你讨论一下化验结果 才知道发生了什么
I wanted to discuss your results and I didn't know,
可我想 你还是希望知道的
but I thought you would want the chance to be aware,
如果你愿意的话
if you're up to it.
是的 当然了
Yeah, sure. Okay.
我长话短说 是好结果
I won't draw it out. It's a good result
血液检测之后
The journey we went on with the amniocentesis
我们做的羊膜穿刺术显示…
after what the blood test showed us…
一切都很健康
everything looks healthy
好的 那就好
Okay. Good
那好 你一切都好吗 有出现异物或者流血吗
Great. And you're still well? No spotting, no bleeding?
不 没有
No. No.
很好
Okay.
那么 根据你的所有检查结果
Well, in terms of all the results I have for you
没有什么需要担心的
there is nothing I think we should be concerned about.
好的
Okay.
很好  -那么 达维娜会跟你联系
Great.   -So, Davina will reach out
预约第20周的检查
to make an appointment for your 20-week scan.
可我现在 有在担心你
But I'm thinking of you at this time
如果有什么我能效劳的…
And if there's anything I can do.
好的 谢谢你 莎伦
Okay. Great. Thank you. Thanks, Sharon.
继   承   之   战
第 4 季  第 4 集
你把我搞惨了
You know, you fucked me
你他妈把我搞烂了
You fucked me right in the ass here.
朱丽叶 你的所作所为 就是把我捆住
What you've done, Juliet, is you've taken a strap-on
然后狠狠地搞我 知道吗
and you fucked me right in the ass, yeah?
拜托 打给我
Call me. Please.
请坐吧  -谢谢你
Have a seat.   -Thank you
稍后见  -好的
I will see you later.   -Okay.
谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
你好 玛西娅  -你好  肯德尔
Hello, Marcia.   -Hi, Kendall. Hi
节哀顺变
Mes condoleances
Sorry for your loss
谢谢你 你也一样,  -谢谢
Thank you. Uh, likewise.   -Yes
大家备受打击
It's a terrible shock.
没错
Right.
你…你从哪...
And, uh, where... where have you...
你什么时候知道的
When did you get in?
我们每天早上和下午 会联系
We spoke every morning and afternoon,
所以 一听说 我就来了  -好吧
so I came as soon as I heard.   -Okay
我是说
Yeah, I mean, uh...
老实说: 我不知道你们...
I honestly... I didn't think you guys were...
我是说  -我们很亲密
You know?   -We were very close.
很复杂
It was complicated
可是 我们每晚都亲密交谈
but we spoke intimately every evening
好吧 行
Right. Okay
格雷厄姆·珍尼特  -节哀顺变
Graham, Janet.   -We're so sorry
非常感谢
Thank you so, so much
谢谢你们送来花
for your sending of flowers
为你祈祷 肯  -谢谢你
Praying for you, Ken.   -Oh, thankyou
亲爱的 见到你真好
It's so nice to see you, dear one
你好 兄弟  -节哀顺变 肯
Hey, brother.   -Sorry, Ken.
谢谢你 谢谢 希德
Thank you. Thanks, Cyd
节哀顺变
Sorry for your loss
节哀顺变 肯德尔  -谢谢你 佩妮
So sorry, Kendall.   -Thank you, Penny. Thanks.
谢谢 马克
Thanks, Mark.
你好  -你好
Hey.   -Hey.
你还好吗
How you doing?
你好  -你好
Hey.   -Hey.
玛西娅是怎么回事
What's up with Marcia?
舞会上的美女吗  -死亡很搭她
Oh, the belle of the ball?   -Death becomes her.
还有...凯莉去哪儿了
And, like, where... where's... You know, where's Kerry?
在玛西娅的后备箱里
In Marcia's trunk
被毒蛇吃了 在石棺里
Inside an anaconda. Inside a sarcophagus
按照爸的日程表来看
You know that Marcia hasn't seen Dad
玛西娅已经七个星期没见过他了
in, like, seven weeks. Says on his calendar.
他们每晚亲密通话
Intimate calls every night
你们知道吗  -不知道
Did you get that one?   -No.
我应该起诉她
I think I might sue her
让我以为 爸在电话性爱
for making me think of Dad doing phone sex
不说点什么吗
No?
不了 如果你想的话 我也可以侃一段
Yeah. No. I could do a phone sex bit if you want
恐怕你是没有那个心情听
I just thought you wouldn't be in the mood
我实际上…很好
Yeah, I'm actually... I'm fine
虽然我确定它最终会击垮我
Like, I'm sure it'll crush me, eventually
货运火车来了 可是今天我...我还好
Freight train a -coming! But today I'm... Yeah, I'm okay.
是吗 是的
Yeah?   -Yeah.
我觉得好累
I feel knocked out.
没错  -我没睡觉
Yeah.   -I didn't sleep.
我猜 是不是我已经想过太多次了
I wonder if maybe I've just thought about it so much
这样或者那样
one way or another that I don't know
我可能已经提前悲伤过了  -那挺好的
I've maybe pre  -grieved.   -Well, good for you. I mean,
我不相信你 可是
I don't believe you, but...
不
No. Well
无论如何 我们应该聚在一起
Either way, we should, you know, huddle
因为...  -是的
'cause...   -Yeah, yeah
对于我们中的一些人 今天很悲伤 然而对于另一些人
for some of us, it's a sad day. But for others
这是大爆破加冕日
it's Coronation Demolition Derby
日程怎么安排的
What's the schedule?
电话会议应该在11点
Work call is 11:00, I think.
大家还好吗
Hey. How we doing?
没有他在
It's so strange being here.
感觉好奇怪  -是的
Yeah.   -... without him.
没错 没错 我错过了什么
Indeed. Indeed. So, what have I missed?
很多来电
A lot of incoming
很多很多电话  -是的
Lot of incoming.   -Yes.
总统们 首相们
Presidents. Prime ministers.
是的 努力保持一切平稳
Yep. Just trying to keep everything stable.
董事会将在一个小时后连线 选出新的老大
Board on the line in, what, an hour, to pick a new top dog
你什么感觉 弗兰克 谁会是新的 CEO
And what's your sense, Frank? What are the, uh, CEO vibes?
有谁愿意来…
Would anyone care for...
参观一下瓷器吗
a look at the china?
他本打算把那屋子里 一半的人都炒了的
He was gonna fire half that room.
大家都知道吗 我们应该说出来吗
Do people know that? Should we get that out there?
不 不要搞成一场闹剧
No. We don't want it to look like a shit show
虽然这是个混乱的故事
You know, it's chaos narratives...
自相残杀的故事 和垃圾故事
fratricide narratives, bad narratives
家人们  -你好
Hey. Hey. guys.   -Hi.
天哪
Oh, man.
我...我很抱歉 请节哀顺变
I'm... I'm sorry. I'm sorry for your loss.
谢谢  -谢谢你
Thanks, man.   -Thank you
还好 我们大家可以...
It's just great that we can all...
家人们可以互相支持 共渡难关
The family can support each other and stay strong through this
是的  -谢谢 格雷格
Yeah.   -Thanks, Greg
我的家人
My guys.
我亲爱的家人
My lovely guys.
行了 行了 你应该知道
Okay. Hey, hey. You know, we're not, like,
我们没有从小一起长大 好吗 我们的父亲刚去世
playing Chutes and Ladders. Okay? Our dad just died.
所以... 确实对不起
-And...   -No, I'm sorry
我很悲伤
I'm sad.
只是在想 事情会怎么发展
And just thinking about how things will shake down
董事会马上要召开了...
Right? There's the board meeting coming up...
我和尤恩聊过了 他有发言权
any minute, and I talked to Ewan and he'll have a say
所以...  -你...你需要一个
So...   -You... You need to get
新的妈妈 知道吗
a new mommy. Okay?
我们不是你的妈妈
We're not your mommy.
我要...我要接电话了 能麻烦你
I'm... I'm getting a call here. Could you maybe...
谢谢 格雷格  -我是真心的 认真的
Thanks, Greg.   -Yeah. No, I mean it. Seriously.
快滚吧 谢谢你  -抱歉了
Fuck right on off. Thank you.  -Sorry, guys.
是马特森 我要接吗
Matsson. Do I?
接吧
Yeah.
我们先 我们…
Let's just... Let's... Let's...
准备一下...  -好
just do five...   -Yeah
让我们把事情理顺 我们...
And get our ducks in a row. Yeah? I mean, we...
不然我们他妈没考虑好 说出的话 他一旦放在网络上
We fucking blurt and he puts it on his socials
我们捡了芝麻丢了西瓜
and suddenly we sold Manhattan for glass beads
对吗  -好吧 我让它响着吧
Right?   -Okay. I'll let it ring out
所以目标是今天我们要发表声明
So, the aim is, we'd like to make an announcement today
宣布谁会在过渡时期接管公司
Stating who we think would take over in the interim
在周一上任  -没错 我的立场是
ready for Monday.   -Right. And here's my position
我想知道 我们是否需要掌控公司
I wonder if we don't wanna take control of the plane here.
是的...当务之急是跟GOJO的交易
Yeah, well. The... I guess the first thing is the GoJo deal.
董事会股东们 每个人都很迫切
The board, the shareholders, everyone's very keen.
所以...  -没错 说实话
So...   -No, exactly. And I tell you,
我非常担心继承人们对这次交易的重视程度
I worry about the kids' commitment to the deal
如果我们召集董事会 弗兰克
If we called around the board, Frank
你对临时任命决定的影响力会很大
you would hold a lot of sway on the interim appointment
他们确实需要高级管理层的意见
They'd like senior management input, yeah
没错 如果我们传递的信息类似于
Right, and if the message we gave was to be, you know,
但是 继承人们都...
"But that the kids are... are...
是一群变态的蠢货
Screw ups and dipshits.
应该是在此时此刻
Maybe, uh, not constitutionally
没有完全做好准备...
well  -equipped at this point...
...接任该项职位  -没错
to take on the role    -Yeah.
我猜 下一个问题会是
I guess the question then, uh, would just be
我们更支持谁
"Who might we favor?'
当然是格丽 她是安全牌
Gerri, obviously, is a safe pair of hands
而且近期她接任过  -是的
She's done it recently.   -Yeah.
虽然 但是通常来讲
Although, obviously, generally speaking.
首席财务官才是最好的临时接任者
the CFO might be considered the natural interim
没错
Yeah.
我猜 你已经开始在筹谋大计了吧
I guess you've already had your tilt at the windmill on here.
没错 我以前接任过 还挺成功的
Exactly. I've already done it. And quite successfully
这就是个暂时的角色
And it's an interim role...
为了完成交易而已 我会保证交易顺利的
to do the deal. I'd get it done
为你平安落地提供最好的保障 卡尔
Buckle you into your golden parachute, Karl.
哇...
Well...
别这么着急把我排除在外啊 格丽
Don't push me out the plane so fast there, Gerr.
老家伙刚走
Well, with the old man gone.
我忍不住思考 我还有什么可以奉献的
I can't help but wonder if I don't have a little left to give.
我觉得你是企业的传奇人物
Look. I think you're a corporate legend
你在九十年代做的关于有线网络的事情
What you did in the '90s with cable?
让人震撼  -洛根厌恶你
Huge.   -Logan was souring on you.
洛根已经不在了
Well, Logan's not around anymore
我想对各位尊敬的...  -好的
I would just like to say...   -Yeah
…高级管理层 说的是
...to this senior group of very respected greybeards
我本人只想
that all I have ever personally asked
有个机会做出点贡献
is the chance to serve.
我的意思是 我不想哀悼了
I mean, I'm sick with grief.
你不想哀悼了吗  -但是我...
You're sick with grief?   -  -But I...
那你最好把这块鱼肉卷放下
Well, you might wanna put down that fish taco
因为你的悲伤之情 通过食欲 散发得到处都是
You're getting your melancholy everywhere.
绝 但是 真的...
Very funny, but...
如果有这样一个机会
were the opportunity to arise,
假如真的有这样一场竞争
all I would say is that if there's a ring
我会心怀感恩地登台
my hat's in, respectfully.
要我说的话
Well, I would just say, um,
如果我们把你推荐给董事会
if we were to recommend you to the board...
他们可能会这么问
the question they might ask
我...我能帮你假设这个问题吗
would... Can... can... Can I frame the question for you?
站在朋友的角度  -当然了
But as a friend.   -Sure.
那么...你要...  -当然
Just so... so you'd be...  Sure.
做好准备 消极的情形会是这样
... be prepared. The negative case would go.
你是个笨手笨脚的外人 没人信任你
you're a clumsy interloper and no one trusts you.
唯一愿意捞你的人 已经死了
The only guy pulling for you is dead
现在你只是娶了前老板的女儿而已
And now, you're just married to the ex-boss' daughter
并且她已经不爱你了
And she doesn't even like you
所以 准确来说 你彻头彻尾完蛋了
And you are fair and squarely fucked.
天哪 卡尔
Jesus, Karl.
弗兰克
Frank.
我可以借用几分钟吗  -当然 没问题
Can I grab you for a second?   -Oh, sure. Yeah
喂 我是奥斯卡
Hi. This is, uh, Oskar
我帮卢卡斯接电话
on Lukas's phone.
你好 奥斯卡 我是罗曼·罗伊
Oh, hey, Oskar. Uh, this is Roman Roy.
卢卡斯之前打电话给我了 但我想把
Lukas called but I was just rounding up
我的大猩猩朋友们叫来 一起打个招呼
my chimpanzee friends 'cause they wanna say hi too.
他在吗
Is he there?
不 他...他说他现在没空
Oh, uh. No. He, uh... He won't now, he says
好吧 可以
Yeah, okay. All right
那你可以请求他一下吗
Um, so can you get him, please?
他...刚才是他最后一次有空打给你们了
Yeah, well. He was... he was calling last chance,
很抱歉 因为你们懂的...我们这周要开
unfortunately, because, y'know, we... we have this, uh,
公司战略会议
a company strategy sesh this week
你好 我是肯德尔 拜托了兄弟
Hey, this is Kendall. Come on, man.
我们打给你们 是因为我们很诚心
We dropped a call because we wanted to all beon
想一起听电话 你可以去找找他吗
out of respect. Can you grab him?
我们不是在耍花招
It wasn't a power play
当然 兄弟 没事的 我们知道
Oh, sure, man. No, that's cool. No, we know.
这...这不是他的意思
It's, uh... This isn't from him.
只是 他行程真的很紧凑
He's just on a super tight schedule now
好吧 他只是不想打个招呼吗
Okay. Well, does he just not wanna say hi?
他还想买公司吗
You know, is he still buying the company?
当然 兄弟
Oh, sure, man.
也许你们不这么紧逼的话
Maybe, if you don't squeeze too tight. No, no.
他...他很想跟你们交流的
He's, uh... He's excited to speak to you guys
谁会来主导
Who will be leading?
我们还在商量
We're just huddling on that now.
我们是个流动性比较强的团体 是吧
We're a pretty fluid group.   -Yeah.
但是听着 你们的务虚会
But listen, it seems like maybe
似乎来得正是时候
your retreat has come at a good time.
是吗
Yeah?
你们整理好思路
You guys get your ducks in a row.
我们整理好团队 选好领队
We do our board, pick our captain.
我们可以一周之后重新商量
We can reconfigure in a week or whatever
好的 我们不想...我们不想失去这个势头
Yeah. Well, we d... we don't... we don't wanna lose momentum.
好的 我们也不想
Uh  -huh. Okay. No, nor us
你...你们应该知道昨天发生了什么
Y... you obviously know what happened here
对吗
yesterday, right?
当然 我们为你们感到非常惋惜
Oh, sure. Yeah, yeah. We really feel for you guys
太糟糕了
Bad one.
是的 是的 谢谢你的好意 多谢了
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, bad one. Thank you for that. Thanks
是的 但是你们可以不管是谁
Yeah. Yeah. But, you know, could you guys
或者是你们公司的高层之一
or whoever, one of the old guys you have,
一天之内来这里跟我们谈吗
like, be here in 24 hours to do this?
抱歉...我们的父亲刚刚才去世
Y... Sorry, our... our dad just died
马上还要面临选举
and we have the election coming up.
你觉得 你们可以来美国跟我们见面吗
How would you feel about doing a meet in the U.S.?
我们这是...年度务虚会
To have here... This... This is the annual retreat.
我们不能抛下不管
We can't just drop it
没关系 我知道的 好的
No. I totally see that. Fine.
玛西娅  -怎么了
Marcia.   -Yeah.
我为你感到非常惋惜
I am so sorry for your loss
谢谢 看到他们跑步的样子了吗
Thankyou. See how they run.
看到了 像小老鼠一样碎步跑
Yes. Scurrying like little rats.
你好 玛西娅
Hi, Marcia.
你好,  -我们感到非常惋惜
Hi.   -I'm so sorry for your loss.
谢谢
Thank you.
你也是 康纳
To you too, Connor.
好的 你好
Okay. Hi.
谢谢  -玛西娅 我们等会再聊
Thank you.   -Marcia, we'll catch up later
好的 当然  -好的
Yeah, of course.   -Okay
好吧
Okay.
恭喜  -谢谢
Congratulations.   -Thank you
看看 你走现在真不容易  -对
Look how far you've come.   -Yup
我们都不容易 对吗
Well, look at us both. Right?
真的很抱歉 我的意思是
I'm sorry about everything. I mean,
你们才刚办完婚礼 就要来这种场合
after your wedding, to have to do this
我们下周就出发了
Uh, we're gonna head off next week
我们计划了一个小假期
You know, we've got a little trip planned out.
威斯康星  明尼苏达
Wisconsin, Minnesota,
密歇根 宾夕法尼亚
Michigan, Pennsylvania
就是我们要去度蜜月的洲
Mm, the honeymoon states
抱歉
Yeah, sorry
我想说...  -行
I'm just gonna...   -Right
我想说 因为...
I wanted to say, because.
一切都会发生得很快
these things could happen in a flash
但是 如果到了 你想把这个
But if and when the time comes
房子卖了的时候
for you to consider selling this place
我会...
I would be...
我甚至不敢开口
I'm worried to even say the words
但是我...我想...我...  -没必要不好意思
But I... I would be... I...   -No need to be ashamed
我们是家人
We're family.
我预期的价格 在六千万到七千万之间
I will be looking for between 60 and 70 million.
这样啊 那好
Oh, right. Okay.
是的  -那么...
Yeah.   -So, like...
差不多六千三或者...  -成交
Sixty three or...  -Done.
成交吗  -对 成交
Done?   -Yeah. Done.
好的
Okay.
好啊
Yeah.
成交 太棒了
Done.  Great.
卡尔
Karl, hey.
过来下 我有话跟你说
Come here a second. I wanna talk to you about something
我作为遗嘱执行人 我拿到了一份
In my role as executor, I've, uh, had passed to me
很令人不安的文件
a rather worrying piece of paper
好吧 那...
Okay. And...
还有谁知道这事
Who else knows?
目前为止 据我所知 只有你我二人
As of now, as far as I know, just you and me.
你有什么想法
So what are you thinking?
说实话 你过来之前
Well, I honestly didn't even wanna start thinking
我都没开始思考
till you were here.
我是说 能不能让它消失
I mean, could it, might it just go away?
可能它被弄丢了
I mean, it might get lost
我当然希望不会
I hope it doesn't.
但如果你的手微微颤抖
But what if your hand goes a little wobbly
让风把它刮走了
and the draft takes it away
然后不小心冲进了马桶
and it gets flushed down a toilet by mistake
当然 我只是开个玩笑  -当然 你是...
I'm kidding, of course.   -No, sure, you're.
你这是在设想喜剧
You're speculating in a comic mode.
是啊 幽默一下
Yeah. In a humorous vain
我们不会让小公主把事情搞砸的
We're not gonna let the little princess screw things up.
对吧 弗兰克 如果格丽想阻碍我 那我就走人
Right, Frank? If Gerri's going to block me, I want out.
我要我的退休方案
I want my fucking package
我和我姐夫...
I am halfway in on a Greek island
正准备买个希腊小岛呢
with my brother in-law.
小伙子们 怎么了  -你好
Say, what's up, boys?   -Hi.
好吧
Okay
我刚拿到了这张纸 格丽
I've just been handed a piece of paper, Gerri
这是...上面列了
It's, uh... It has a list of wishes
洛根的遗愿清单
in the event of Logan's death
葬礼安排之类的  -我能看看吗
Funeral arrangements, so on.   -May I?
第三段
Paragraph three.
是在哪儿找到的
And where was this found?
他的私人保险箱
In his private safe
这 用铅笔写的附录 是什么
And this penciled addendum is what?
我们没碰过 铅笔写的下划线是他加的
We haven't touched it. The underline in the pencil is his
显然 没有写日期
Undated, apparently
也没有与他的律师和我分享过 所以:
Not even shared with his lawyer or myself, so.
所以 你有什么想法
So, what are you thinking?
从法律上讲 由于家族没有完全控制权
Well, legally, since the family doesn't have full control,
从法律上讲 这  -法律上讲
Iegally, it... it wouldn't...   -Legally
应有董事会决定 由谁接任 所以…
it's up to the board to decide who's next, so...
对  -这文件是不相关的
Right.   -this is not germane.
对 这文件无关 无关
Right, it's not germane. Not germane.
我们开玩笑说 它可能掉进马桶里
We were joking that it could fall in the toilet
是啊 那可太招笑了
Yes. Well, that is a very funny joke
你知道吗
You know,
他们说 葬礼之后 马上做重大决定 并不好
they say it's a bad idea to make big decisions right after
对 但他们也说
Sure. But they also say
不付房产中介费 是很明智的
it's pretty smart not to pay realtors fees.
想入住这种好房子 可不容易
And it's such a bitch to get into these good buildings.
好吧
All right, well.
大家好
Hey, guys.
老康
Hey, Con.
你们还好吗
How are you faring?
你还好吗  -你也知道的
How are you?   -Oh, you know.
看到讣告了吗
Seen the obits?
当然 你喜欢环球报登的照片吗
Sure. You like the Globe photo?
你们有人见过他笑成那样吗
Did any of you guys ever see him laugh like that?
只有流浪汉身上着火的时候才会
Only if a hobo was on fire.
是啊 说实话 他们把爸爸说得好棒
Yeah. I mean, to be honest, uh, Dad sounds amazing.
让我都想重新认识一下了
I'd like to have met Dad.
你们真的还好 对吧
But you guys are okay, really?
还好
Yeah.
罗曼已经提前伤心过了 还在公司的时候
Yeah, Roman has pre-grieved. Already gave at the office.
他们都他妈不信我
They don't fucking believe me
从我的角度来看
You know, from where I'm sitting.
天真的人 是你们 好吗
you're the ones that look naive, okay?
我一直担心会发生这种事
I've been worried that this was gonna happen for ages
你还好吗
How you do in'?
我毫无头绪
I have no clue.
我还好  -是吗
I'm okay.   -Yeah?
对 我还好
Yeah, I'm okay.
你还好吗  -我吗
You okay?   -Me?
你会笑我的 但是在凌晨
You're gonna laugh but in the middle of the night
做了个谈话
I did a talk
谈话疗程 我的心理医生推荐了一个人
like, a session. My therapist recommended someone,
我找到他 然后...他还挺不错的
and I got to him and he's... he's kind of good
你们需要的话 我有他的电话
I have his number if you want
我知道这很蠢 但有些事是你们可以做的
Like, it's dumb but there's actually things you can do
听起来 你找到了最棒的悲伤倾诉人
I mean, sounds like you've got the best grief guy
我有个很棒的悲伤倾诉人 去你的
I have a great grief guy. Fuck you.
你能搞定的
You're gonna destroy this
大家伙 来了更多的新闻
Hi, guys. Uh, some more hard copies.
讣告  -评论来了啊
Obituaries.   -The reviews are in.
太棒了
Great.
是啊 大部分都是五星好评
Yeah. They're mostly five stars.
我预计董事会将在中午召开
And I think the board will assemble now at noon.
好的 谢谢雨果
Okay, thanks, Hugo.
肯  -怎么了
Okay. Ken.   -Yeah?
我能...问你点事吗
Can I, um... Can I ask you something?
稍微耽误一下 抱歉 非常快
Just for one second, sorry, just something quickly
好 很快就好
Yeah.   -Just take a second
还要私下问
Private.
肯 我可能
Ken, um, I may have, um...
卷进了某件事情
caught myself up in a little bit of something
可能问题不大 但是
Probably nothing but, uh.
我...很抱歉 用这事打扰你
I'm... I'm sorry to bother you with this.
什么事
Okay. What?
我刚发现 我女儿
Ijust found out that my daughter
她碰巧在你父亲去世的消息
she happened to sell a bunch of Waystar stock
公开之前 抛售了一批...
just before the news about your father went, um...
韦斯达的股票
went public
完全是巧合
A total coincidence.
但我...不想让它变成一个问题
But I, uh... I don't want it to come up as an issue, y'know?
你那天跟她交谈过吗
Did you speak to her on the day?
通话记录里面都有什么
What are the phone records gonna say?
我不记得了
I can't recollect.
雨果
Hugo.
我跟朱丽叶关系很疏远
I don't even have a relationship with Juliet
这是个悲伤的事实
that's the sad fact
讽刺的是 我们很少聊天 而且...
The irony is, we hardly talk and, uh...
谢谢 肯
Thanks, Ken.
有什么精彩的
Anything good?
信使报 你得需要
The Courier. You need a...
一个密码本 才能看懂 准备好了吗
code book for this one. You ready?
好了
Yeah.
一个复杂的人
"A complicated man."
向员工扔手机
Threw phones at staff
挺有趣的  -“对国民情绪拥有敏锐嗅觉”
It's good.   -"Sharp reader of the national mood."
他有点种族歧视
He's a bit racist.
还有"他是那个时代的杰出人物”
Well, then. "He was very much a man of his era.
再说一次 种族歧视
Again, racist.
而且 容忍性侵事件
Also, relaxed about sexual assault.
商业天才
"Business genius."
没给美国交过半毛钱的税
Never paid a penny in U.S. Tax.
那真是...  -太炸了
Oh, that's... Yeah.   -Boom.
"人脉很广"
"Well connected"
"人脉很广" 这不太公正了
"Well connected" Now, that's not fair.
我感觉这词是…
I feel like well  -connected is...
通常是恋童癖的委婉说法
generally accepted to be a euphemism for pedophile
从没人暗示过他.
and no one ever suggested that he would, you know...
会操小孩  -确实
Fuck a child.   -Yeah
是啊
Yeah.
他连自己孙儿都不抱
He wouldn't even hug his grandkids.
大伙打扰了 我觉得他们想在图书室见你们
Hey, guys. Sorry. I think they wanna see you up in the library.
好 咱们走
All right, let's go.
谢了
Thanks
你好啊 肯
Hey, Ken.
你好 汤姆  -肯 我只想说
Hey, Tom.   -Hey, um, Ken, Ijust wanted to say, you know
我们之间确实发生了很多很多事
I know there's a lot of water under the bridge, a lot of history
但 在我看来...父亲大人走了
But as far as I am concerned, the... the big man passing
那些也都会一笔勾销 对吧
cleaned the slate. So, yeah. I just... Yeah.
我只想和你说这个 我希望
I just wanna say that and you know, I wish, maybe
我可以收回
there's some things...
之前说过的一些话
I could maybe take back, some words
很遗憾你失去令尊 但我希望你知道
And I'm sorry for your loss. But I want you to know
我在这里...随时待命
that I'm... that I'm here to serve. Right here
我喜欢你 汤姆
I like you, Tom.
祝你好运
Good luck.
来了  -你们好
Hey.   -Hello.
你们好  -进来坐吧
Hello.   -Yeah. Come on in. Have a seat.
你们好吗 我们来了 好不
What's up? Yeah, I know. We're in. Okay?
就不坐了 你们怎么样
No, thanks.   -How are you doing?
还能撑下去  -听着
Yeah. Hanging in.   -So, look.
我是你父亲的遗嘱执行人
I'm one of the executors of your dad's affairs.
这不是法律事务
This is not a legal matter.
但我们发现 他还有其他遗愿
But certain wishes have been discovered
似乎在某年某月 具体日期没有标注
And it appears at a certain point, undated,
你们的父亲看上去是希望
it was suggested that it was your dad's wish that
肯德尔接任首席执行官一职
Kendall take over as CEO.
什么时候写的  -是在保险箱里发现的
Uh  -huh. From when?   -Well, it was in the safe.
夹在雷马达收购案
Between pieces on the Raymada acquisition
和第一美属维京群岛重整案之间
and the first U.S. Virgin Islands reorganizations.
很久了  -有...
So, it's...   -It's old. It's... it's
据我们所知 应该是四年前写的
So, as far as we can tell, from four years ago or so
然后 还有一些
Yeah. Then, it looks like there are
后来用铅笔追加的内容 我...
pencil addendums from another time, I...
我们不知道这个的状态 而且...
We don't know its status. And I mean...
它不具备任何法律效力
it doesn't hold any legal value.
我们想让你们知道这个东西
But we wanted you to know
但也不想特别强调它的重要性
but we wouldn't want it to feel more significant than it should
因为你们家族不再拥有韦斯达的多数控制权
Because the family no longer has majority control
所以 此类提议不具备法律效力
of Waystar, so any such suggestions are non  -binding
我爸是集团创始人
Dad was the founder
所以吧  -当...当然
So...   -O... of... of course,
这是很久前写的 很多情况都变了
it is from some time ago and things changed
洛根是个多变的人
And Logan was a man of different moods
对 对
Yeah. Yeah.
这里有些用铅笔追加写的
There are some additions in pencil
艺术品补充条款
that he put in about artifacts.
我觉得吧... 我能看看吗
And I think...  Can I?
我们觉得从上下文来看
We think from context,
这应该是在过去的一年半里加的
uh, they were added maybe in the last 18 months
那他是最近加了这条下划线吗
So, he underlined recently?
是加下划线还是划掉啊  -小西
Underlined or crossed out?   -Shiv
不是的 我不是赞成或反对
Oh, no, no, no. I'm not saying for or against
只是想...事实上.
I'm just... As a matter of fact, it's.
你认真的吗  -我是说
Are you serious?     -I mean,
毕竟这看起来...  -好了 好了
I mean, it's kinda...   -Okay. Okay
给我看看
let me see the thing
不管是下划线还是划掉.
It's underlined or crossed out, it doesn't.
其实都不重要 因为...
It doesn't really matter because it's...
法律上来讲 只有董事会
Legally, it's the board,
能决定  -没错
yeah, who will choose.   -Exactly
市场 股东 董事会
The market, the shareholders, the board
大家都希望能谈成交易
we all want the sale to go through
这也就是个过渡时期的职务
So, it's an interim position, really
当然 我的意思是 谁都能担任
Sure. I mean, anyone could do that.
既然他说...我是说.
And since he said... I mean... I mean,
他已经说了...  -肯
he has said...   -  -I mean, Ken.
我明白你意思 但这张纸太古老了
Sure, man. I get it. But like, this... this thing is old
而且自那以后 你想送他坐牢
and you've tried to put him in jail, like.
差不多有十多回的样子...  -我...
twelve times since then. So...   -
我想弄清楚的是.
I wonder what was the, you know...
是下划线还是划掉
the underlining or the crossing out
另外 不注明日期
and the unknown age
这不就是...无效文件吗
if it... The document isn't essentially moot
你知道...这无法解读了
You know, it's im... Impossible to decipher
反正这张破纸上没写"小西”
Well, it sure as fucking shit doesn't say "Shiv."
行  -那他
Okay.   -So, what else
还写什么了...你能介绍...我不想.
is in the fucking... Can you... I don't wanna...
葬礼音乐 在纽约下葬 天主教仪式 你看
Music, burial in the city, Catholic. You can see.
要我找格雷格吗
Should I get Greg now?
把这事弄清楚
Just clear this up
失陪一下
Excuse me.
这里还有些公事 也包括私事
There's a mix of, uh, business and personal.
他给科林留了块表
A watch for Colin.
老实说 看上去是他自己起草的
Honestly, it looks like he drafted it himself
都没有给律师 就那么放在保险柜单
never sent it to his lawyer and just put it in the safe
我是说
I mean, mo... more of
这更像是记录灵感
a selection of musings, really
有对税务情况的想法
Some thoughts on the tax position
还有对收藏品的想法  -他...都有什么收藏
or some artwork in storage.   -What... what does he have?
他为了投资 买的一堆印象派的画
He's got, like, a shit ton of, like, investment impressionisms
是吧 好像有三幅高更的画
Right? Like, he's got, uh, three Gauguins
为了躲税 没让别人看过
no one's seen for tax reasons, so
我觉得 他的建议是
I think his suggestion was
为了避税
it might be smart tax-wise
最好把画留在日内瓦保险库
to just leave them in the Geneva vault
去他的 还不如烧了 找保险公司理赔去
Oh, fuck it. Why not just burn them for the insurance, no?
那财务方面可就美梦成真了
Yeah, that would be the dream. Financially speaking
大家好  -对了
Hey, everyone.   -Yes
格雷格  -格雷格
Hey, Greg.   -Greg
你们好
Hey.
以防走漏消息
In case it comes out
我们先告诉你 有张纸上写了你的名字
we wanted you to be aware that you're on a piece of paper
是洛根写的 关于他的心愿
Uh, a side letter left by Logan with.
和开销的补充条款,  -好的
some wishes and disbursements.   -Okay. Yeah
关于...什么的 什么方式
In... in what, uh, capacity? In... in what fashion?
你的名字在 写的杂项里
You're in addendum of miscellaneous matters
用铅笔写的...
in pencil.
还有一个问号  -虽然 但是
with a question mark.   -Nevertheless.
爸可能曾经希望我接替他
Dad may have said he wanted me to take over.
就是说 有一种合理的推断是
And so then, maybe the natural conclusion might perhaps be
我是他的替代
I'd be his number two.
想得挺美 孩子
Nice try, kid.
他写下来 可能是怕 忘了你的名字
He... he probably wrote it down so he can remember your name
我们关系很好的,  -你们关系还很好哪
We had a good rapport.   -You had a good rapport?
我觉得 他不太想看见你
I feel like he already wanted to see less of you
他应该不是想
That's probably, like, 50/50
开除你 就是想杀了你
fire Greg or kill Greg.
我觉得这个问号不是那个意思
I think that it's not that kind of question mark.
有可能是...在思索
I think it's uh um possibly...it's a wonder
那不过是信手乱涂 我们只是通知你
It's a doodle. We just wanted you to be aware.
大家
Oh, hey.
抱歉 玛西娅让我告诉你们
Sorry. Marcia wanted me to let you know that there's some words
有个非正式的...  -好的
down, some informal...   -Okay
有好多事要考虑
Well, there's a lot to consider.
要不 我们董事会之前再碰头
Should we reconvene before the board meeting
交换意见吧  -好
to pool thoughts?   -Yeah
就这样
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
是真的吗 弗兰克
Is it real, Frank?
我不知道
I don't know.
爸想要我接管吗
My dad wanted me to take over?
这个吧
Well,
有时候 他有时真这么想 你知道的
sometimes. You know that he did. Sometimes.
他让我痛恨他 然后就死了
He made me hate him, then he died.
我以为他不喜欢我
I feel like he didn't like me.
我让他失望了
I disappointed him
不是的 别瞎想
No. No. Come on.
我们总会想象可怕的东西
We think these grand horror things,
就是这种时刻 那些冰棚
at times like these, these ice shelves are gonna
夜里突然出现 把我们脑袋切掉 都不是真的
come at us in the night and take our heads off. It's not true.
他是个混蛋老头 但是他爱你
He was an old bastard. And he loved you
他是爱你的
He loved you.
你真这么想
You think?
没错
I think so.
如果我争取到他们的支持 你会加入吗
If I get them in behind me, will you follow?
肯 你已经酝酿了其他计划
Ken, you've got stuff cooking
看起来势头良好
You seem so well.
你真的准备回来吗
You really want back in?
我心里想
Part of me is just like
要不干脆就让那个可怜的孤儿如愿以偿好了
"Well, let's just give the poor orphan what he wants."
抱歉 我也不知道我怎么了 这样说不好
Sorry, I don't know what's wrong with me. That's not good
没必要 我懂 我懂的
No, no, no. I get it, yeah
这只是临时职位
I mean, it is interim.
好吧
Well...
希望如此
So long as it is
你什么意思 你想说什么
What do you mean? What are you thinking?
我们之间还算不错吧
It's felt good. Us, right?
当然  -但现在...
Yeah.   -And now, does this.
感觉还好吗 刚才那事让你感觉好吗
feel good? Like, does that feel good? It's.
你怎么样了
How're you doing?
不好说
I don't know
你呢
You?
尽管他不是我的老爹 不过
Well, he wasn't my dad but, you know,
还是...
he's...
很令人难过
It's sad.
没错
Yeah.
我想 你把赌注押错了
I guess you already picked the wrong horse
你把赌注押在了一匹死马上了  -别这样
You might've picked the dead horse.   -Don't
你会后悔的 我们不如友善点说话
You'll regret it. Let me show you some kindness.
这可不是我的风格
Not my thing.
老实说
You know, honestly.
我已经
I guess I'm just,
慢慢地开始接受事实
Slowly coming to accept that.
其实是我们害死了他  -小西
we killed him.   -Shiv.
没错 就是我们 他在飞机上去世了
No, we did. He died on the plane
要不是因为我们
And he wouldn't have been on the plane
他也不会坐上那架飞机
except that we made him get on there
这确实是个很冷酷的现实  -世事难料
So that's just very cool.   -Anything could've happened
你也不可能料想到 会发生这样的事
A million things could've happened
我只是不想给自己开脱
I just don't wanna fake myself out.
如果我们答应了GOJO的条件
If we had said yes to GoJo, then...
他可能还能活个二十年
he might've been around for 20 more years
还有机会哄孙子睡觉
So he could rock his grandkids to sleep
正如他"梦寐以求"的那样
As he was evidently so keen to do.
没错
Yeah.
不过 现在说什么都晚了 不是吗
Well, that's fucked now, isn't it? So.
别 别这样
Don't. Just stop
我有点恼火
I'm angry.
老爹走了 我妈更糟糕
My dad died. And my mom is a fucking disaster.
我的丈夫也…
And my husband is
还有凯莉 玛西娅...
And Kerry, and Marcia, and.
我感觉 只有我一个人 失去所有
It... it... it feels like I'm the only one who lost something
真正在乎的东西
that they actually fucking
而且 这些东西再也不会回来了
wanted here and it's not coming back, so...
对
Yeah
西沃恩 你还记得
Siobhan, do you remember when
我们第一次见面的时候吗
we first knew one another?
在法国的时候 我第一次坐飞机去见你
The first time in France when I flew to you?
在那段 对你来说 同样煎熬的时期
And it was that very difficult time for you
我还给你寄了那些亲笔手写的纸条
And I'd sent you... all those handwritten notes.
还有第一次
And then the first time
你穿着那件美丽的丝绸衬衫
that you were wearing that very... fine silk shirt
我把手接在你的肩膀上
And I put my arm around you
不停地问你 “你喜欢这样吗
I said, I kept asking, "Do you like this?
你喜欢吗”
Do you like this?"
最后你说 “我都喜欢”
And you said, eventually, "I like it all."
当然记得...
Yeah, well...
那已经是很久前的事了
That was a while ago, wasn't it?
没有想象中那么久
Not that long
确实是很久以前的事了
No, it was a while back
科林还穿牛仔裤吗  -看起来是的
Colin does jeans?   -Yeah.
你看他那副不知所措的样子 手都不知道放哪
He doesn't know what the fuck to do with himself. Look at his arms.
就像找不到主人的狗子
He looks like a dog without its person
有意思
Fun.
科林有孩子了吗
Colin has a kid?
老天 还真没注意
Shit. Didn't even notice.
这是怎么回事  -你怎么看
What the fuck now?   -What do we think?
怎么...屋子里怎么有只狗
There's a dog... There's a dog in the house
玛西娅
Marcia.
玛西娅这只汪汪队成员是怎么回事
Marcia, so, what's with the... the "Ruff-ruff"?
特勤局正在全面搜查这个地方
The Secret Service are conducting a sweep.
杰瑞德·门肯 已经在来的路上了
Jeryd Mencken is en route
我想今天还是算了吧
I'm not sure that I want that today actually
我不想看见他  -没错 他执意要来
I don't wanna see him.   -Yeah, he asked
他是你们父亲的好友 不是吗
He was a friend of your father's, no?
得了吧 他们是有说过话 但只不过是谈生意
Come on. They spoke. But no, it-was transactional
没错 不像他那圈子里的兄弟
Yeah. Not like all his real friends
那些真心的朋友
from his men's group and choir
他的两个死党  -得了吧 罗曼 他们根本就不熟
His two best friends.   -Come on, Rome. He didn't know him
他们俩 一个叫“那个谁” 一个叫“死远点
'What's-his-face" And "Get-that-fucker-away-from-me."
他把他叫做怪胎
He called him the spooky embryo
那好 听我说
Yeah, okay. Look. It's
你看看这满屋子的行尸走肉
just there's all these fucking ghouls here.
算了吧  -我不想看到
So, come on.   -I just don't wanna see
他那副假惺惺又傲慢的嘴脸
his smirky, little autocratic face.
下周这个时候 搞不好他就是总统了
Probably gonna be president this time next week.
好的 我认为我有一票否决权 我老爹刚去世了
Okay. Well, I think I have a veto. My dad just died
我觉得我也有一票否决权
I think I have a counter veto
好巧不巧 我老爹也刚去世
cause, weirdly, my dad just died too
伙计们 从 未来生意的角度考虑
Guys, I think on a business level,
我们不能失去他这个人脉
we need to have a relationship
是吗 你真这么想
Yeah. You do?
现在你想他这个人脉了吗
Now you do, huh?
这下好了
Yeah.
朋友们 老天
Friends.   -God
糟糕的一天  -在场的朋友们
This fucking day.   -Good friends, all.
当一个伟人离世时
When a great man passes
天国的天使也忍不住落泪 但是…
the angels of heaven weep. But when...
当一个保守主义的泰斗离世时
a giant of the conservative movement passes...
老天 我们到哪请的这个跳梁小丑
God. Now, we're having a kids' entertainer?
看他得意地 像个国王的模样
Who the fuck made him the king of the day?
洛根·罗伊就是这样的一位泰斗
Logan Roy was such a giant.
他谦逊 不失风度 正直庄严
He was a man of humility, grace, dignity
却在 从堵塞的马桶里捞手机时
Who died fishing his iPhone
不幸离世了  -面对公众时
from a clogged toilet.   -In public
他不仅是个优秀的演说家  -真的吗
he was a great communicator.   -Really?
还是位优秀的领导者  -天哪
A powerful man.   -Oh, man
听说的 卡尔给压下来了
So they say. Karl blocked it.
不会吧  -他只吃
No.   -The man lives
惊奇牌面包和牛排炸薯条
on Wonder bread and steak frites
而且20年没拉过屎了
He hadn't had a shit for 20 years
他是个有智慧的人
He was a man of wisdom.
虚怀若谷 谦恭自守
A man of humility. A man without vanity
他还从来不穿紧袜
He was a man who wasn't wearing his compression socks
这样才可以在凯莉面前保持性感
So he could look hot for Kerry
…让世界变得更加美好
... to make the world a better place.
他如女娲造人一般 塑造了这个国家
He molded the country like clay in his hands
并赋予了它美丽
and made it into something beautiful
赋予了它美丽的鸡巴  -嘴下留情吧
Into the shape of a dick.   -Come on.
赋予了它力量 赋予了它秩序
He made it stronger. More coherent
当我想到洛根·罗伊 我联想到
When I think of L.R., I think
象征着自由的雄狮  -你听听他在讲什么
of a great lion of freedom.  I.   -Can you believe this shit?
他在把老爹描述成一个新时代保守主义者
He's trying to make Pop into a neoconservative.
他可不是新保守主义者 我看是旧自由主义者
He wasn't a neocon, he was a paleo libertarian
他实际上是无政府资本主义者
He was practically an anarcho-capitalist
当然 如果你喜欢班尼·希尔和辛纳特拉
Yeah, sure. I mean, if you like Benny Hill and Sinatra,
你是不是也变成他们其中一员了
does that make you one of those things?
他们在欺负死人不会说话
They're trying to body snatch him.
历史即将被书写 接下来的48小时尤其关键
History's being written. The next 48 hours are crucial
但愿他一路走好 希望不久后
Godspeed, for surely soon
洛根·罗伊将在极乐世界里播送滚动新闻
Logan Roy will be running rolling news in heaven
还好吗  -你好
How's it going?   -Hey
小西真的很抱歉  -谢谢
Shiv, I'm so sorry.   -Thank you
很抱歉小西  -谢谢
Hey, I'm so sorry, Shiv.   -Thanks
感谢您的出席  -你好
Thankyou for coming.   -Hey
您能来 实在是太好了
Good of you to be here.
我深表遗憾 我父亲也为此非常伤心
Oh, yeah, I'm so sorry. My dad was very affected
哦
Yeah.
冒昧地问一句 你爸的表情为什么是这样
And so, why is he doing that with his face, can I ask?
他近来都是这样的表情
That's just how his face looks these days
真的吗 永恒的微笑
Oh, yeah? Frozen into a smile?
别  -他是伤心的
Please.   -He's... He's sad.
他和您的父亲相识多年
He knew your dad for a long time.
他刚刚…绝对是朝我眨眼了
I'm sure... I'm pretty sure he just fucking winked at me
新闻世界的一角 -桑迪 我是肯德尔
The news world...   -Sandy, it's Kendall
...轰然坍塌
...is broken.
他干嘛呢
What is he doing?
我猜吧
I mean, I guess
他和父亲确实是相交甚密
they were close, Dad and him, so.
加上他手里还有董事会的一票
Yeah. Plus, he still has a board vote.
但 你懂的 你更希望最终是谁
But, you know, I guess, who would you prefer
我们之间 还是那帮老臣
one of us or one of the old guard?
都还好吧  -没事儿
Everything all right?   -Yep
绝了
Oh, dear. Yes
瞧瞧是谁钻出来了
Look who's crawled out of the woodwork
我警告过她别来 真是不理解
I told her not to do this. I don't understand.
我的天 她走过来了
Oh, God. Oh, she's coming over
太没品了
Oh, it's so distasteful
你好  -你好
Hi.   -Hello
我收到你的消息了 我只是想来
I got your message but I just wanna go...
想上楼收拾我的东西 然后带走
I just have some things of mine upstairs that I need
都收拾好了
They're in a bag.
凯文 梅拉尼
Kevin. Melanie.
我只是想上去看看
I just need to go up, so...
请自重 不行  -求你了
Please. No.   -Thank you
你不能上去
Not upstairs.
不要让她上去
I don't want her up.
我就知道  -行了 别冲动
Okay. I know...   -Come on. Easy. Easy
别看了 玛西娅
Don't look, Marcia
这太不和谐了  -出什么事了
it's too unpleasant.  -Sorry, what's uh...
怎么了 你还好吗 这是你的东西吗
What's going on? You okay? Is this yours? You okay?
我没事 没事的
Yeah, I'm good. I'm good
我没事  -那就好 没事吗
I'm... I'm good.   -Cool? You're good?
需要我帮忙吗
Um, do you need me to help you...?
我不确定 我有没有 你的联系方式
Sorry. I don't know if I have your private number.
能告诉我吗
Can you send that to me?
没事的 我来帮你
It's fine. I got it, I got it, I got it
妈的
Goddammit.
我们之前已经聊过结婚的事
We were talking about getting married
他说 他正在安排 你能帮我问一问吗
and he was making arrangements about us, so could you check?
行 好的
Yeah? Yeah, yeah. And, um...
他说 他会起草份文件
He was gonna... He was gonna make a note
给他的律师 或者其他什么人看
He was gonna write his lawyer or something
求你了 帮我问问看
Please, can you check?
可以吗  -我会去问问的 放心
Can you check on it?   -I'm gonna check on it. I got it
我好像没有你的私人电话
Do I have your private number? I think...
去吧 带她从后门离开
Go ahead, take her out the back, yeah?
有我呢 有我呢
I can get it. I can get it.
绝了 有些人掉金豆豆了
Oh, God. Here come the waterworks
从后门出去 比利
Out the back, Billy.
“带她从后门出去 比利” 听起来可真贴心啊
"Take her out the back, Billy." That's always nice to hear, huh?
玛西娅 有这个必要吗
Marcia, that was unnecessary, right?
我们会帮她叫一辆去地铁站的出租车
We're calling Kerry a taxi to the subway
好让她回到她的小公寓去
so that she can go home to her little apartment.
真贴心啊
Nice.
老天爷
Jesus.
和你的老朋友桑迪聊得怎么样,  -挺好的
How's your friend, Sandy?   -Yeah. "Who are you?
就聊些"你是谁 为什么这场淫趴如此沉重”
Why is this sex party so sad?"
小西 我们聊聊吧
Shiv, should we talk?
别这样 什么都不需要变
Yeah. We... we don't need to... Nothing needs to change too much.
无论你想说什么 就直接说吧
Like, whatever you're thinking, you can... you can say
对呢 我们绝对应该聊聊呢
Fine. We should... We should definitely talk. Okay
那什么 罗哥
Hey. Hey, Rome.
最近怎么样  -很好 你呢
How are you doing?   -Hi. Great. How are you?
我也是 我也是
Yeah. I'm good. I'm okay
我只是想说 你要想的话
I just want to say, uh, tell me... tell me to fuckoff
随时可以让我滚蛋 但是
if you like, really, but, you know, the, uh...
那份文件怎么说
the piece of paper situation?
怎么了  -是的 我听说了
Yeah.   -Yeah. I heard about it.
我不想
And I, uh... I didn't wanna...
太逾越
I don't wanna t... talk out of turn.
但我们都清楚 罗根只希望一个人接手
but we both know that Logan only wanted one person
但他刚刚才叫你回来
to take over, and he just asked you back in
看看你吧 我亲爱的小汤汤
Look at you. Tommy -wommy. Tightrope Tommy
摇摇晃晃骑自行车跨越尼加拉瓜大瀑布
Riding his little subtle cycle across Niagara Falls, huh?
小汤汤哦  -我只是想做出点贡献
Tip -toe Tommy.   -Here to serve.
一点小小的贡献
I'm... I'm here to serve.
涂好润唇膏的小汤汤 娇娇嫩嫩地拍老子的马屁
Lip balm, Tom-wom. Lubing up his lips to kiss my butt
来了  -来了 兄弟
Hey.   -Hey, dude
那个老混蛋啊  -确实
That old fucking bastard.   -Yeah
确实
Yeah.
我以为他会像我爸一样
I thought he'd be like my dad.
九十五了 还在想着 告死邻居
Ninety-five and just started suing the neighbor
发生什么了  -肺栓塞
What was it?   -Embolism. Pulmonary
我可是听说
Because I heard he saw
他看到你收购皮尔斯的计划之后 活活笑死了
your Pierce business plan and choked laughing
你个垃圾
You fucking prick
喂
Hey.
别太伤心
Come on.
一切都会好的
It's all right.
别难过
Hey.
那个...
So, uh...
听着
Listen.
你要在这里参加董事会吗
You gonna do the board call from here?
这里或者车上
Uh, here or car
因为 是这样
Because there's, uh...
有一份文件 写着我的名字
there's a piece of paper with me on it.
父亲说 希望我来接手
That Dad said it should be me
是吗
Oh?
那好啊
Okay.
你能站在我这一边吗
Can you swing in for me?
你了解我 了解我的缺点
You know me, you know my flaws.
而且 这只是暂时的
It's short term.
你现在是在拉拢我吗
I mean, you're really selling me right now. I mean...
我想
I guess.
上一次我听了你的话
You know, my pubes got a little singed
差点烧着我的蛋  -我知道
the last time I went with you.   -Yeah
还记得吗  -记得
Remember? Yeah.   -Yeah
听我说 上一回情况不同
Well, yeah. That was, uh... That was a different...
家人在先 我只能那么做
different thing. For my family, I had to back down.
否则 他会不遗余力搞死我的
There was no card he wouldn't play against me.
你到底是不是真的想要交易
Do you even fucking like the deal?
是 听着 这笔交易必须敲定
Yes. Yes, I do. Look, the deal has to happen.
我们不能再留着这堆烂摊子了
We can't live in a haunted house
我们兄妹已经计划好了
I have plans with the sibs
只接手新闻部 或者直接与皮尔斯合并
We... we'll take news and maybe fuse with Pierce,
你知道的 敲定这笔交易
but, you know, it'll be a feather in my cap
才能稳固我的地位
to bring in the deal
你能让他们理解这件事吗 兄弟
And you could bring it home? Dude. Ken
你的大脑还正常吗
Is your fucking head on straight?
都有可能 我的大脑半死半活
I'm twin track. I'm dead but I'm alive.
于是 沉迷工作吗
Yeah? Dive into work?
不然呢 我们还能做什么
Dude, what are we gonna do?
躲在角落里喝闷酒吗
Sit in the dark and d... drink Laphroaig?
那么...
And...
对我 又有什么好处呢 肯
what's in it for me, Ken?
我也不知道
I don't know, man. Maybe do a solid
就当 帮刚刚丧父的老朋友 一个忙
For your oldest pal the day after his dad died
怎么样
How about that?
你喜欢这里吗 妈妈
What do you think of the apartment, Mom?
挺好的
Mm, it's very pleasant
我们得找出所有的承重墙
We need to check all the walls
我想看看 能不能把这个中厅
and see if they're structural. I'd actually like to make this
扩大一些  -威拉的妈妈
you know, bigger.   -Willa's mom.
太可爱了 她快要吃吐了吧
God love her. Her plate is groaning
听着 我觉得斯图伊会支持我们其中之一
Hey, so listen. I think Stewy would swing behind one of us
好吧 她知道能再回去拿吗
Okay. Does she know she can go back?
她把葡萄弄掉了  -是的
And she dropped the grapes.   -Yeah
这下她可算是吃喝不愁了
Her boat really came in, didn't it?
一夜暴富了
This is turning into the grand tour for her.
我想我的议程是 我们是否.
I guess the agenda for me is do we.
我们同意飞去找马特森吗
You know, do we agree to flying to Matsson?
你知道康纳要搬进来了吧
You know that Connor's moving in, yeah?
好吧 怎么回事
Okay. What?
玛西娅继承了房子 但她
Well, Marcia gets it but she kinda
她...她算是卖给我了吧  -是吗
she... she sorta sold it to me.   -She did?
我们都搬进来吧
Let's all move in.
一起慢慢变老
Grow old together,
像查理和巧克力工厂那样 同床共枕
share a bed like Charlie and the Chocolate Factory
距离董事会开始还剩十分钟
We've got, like, ten till board time.
是的 你和妈聊了吗
Yeah, you've spoken to Mom yet?
没有 发过几条短信 小西 能不能...
No. S... swapped messages. Shiv. Should... should.
我们能...我们能谈谈吗
Can we... can we... Should we talk?
彼得·穆尼昂正在飞往西班牙的路上
Peter Munion was flying to Spain
他想改道直接来这里
and he tried to reroute to come directly here
因为他想陪我们共渡难关
because he wanted to be with us at this difficult time.
天啊  -他发信息说
Oh, man.   -He sent a message
“情况很糟”
saying "It's a rum situation,"
我们所有人都无所适从
and, "One in the eye for all of us,"
而且…  -能别无视我吗
and also...   -Can you stop ignoring me?
行行好吧 可以吗
Please, for fuck's sake, huh? Come on, please.
我们谈一谈
Let's talk about it.
我们已经有所进展了 已经有所进展了
We got somewhere. Us. We've got somewhere.
知道吗 我们谈谈吧 我根本不关心结局如何
Yeah? Let's talk about it. I don't even care what happens
但 别因为我们没有事先沟通
but let's not just give it to the fucking keystone fucks
就让那些老家伙坐收渔利
because we didn't talk.
老康
Con.
真的假的  -你不介意吧
Oh, really?   -Do you mind?
不介意  -抱歉 兄弟
Uh  -uh.   -Sorry, man
我的家 就是你们的家
Mi casa es su casa.
那么 你们觉得呢
So, what do you think?
你对我有意见 是因为...
You have an issue with me because
懂的
Yeah.
不要紧
That's fine.
但我希望 是我们中的一个 是的 这也是爸的意思
But I'd like it to be one of us. And yeah, uh, Dad said so.
好 我们可以谈谈 但你能不能别太兴奋了
Okay. Well, let's discuss but can you please just stop jonesing?
这可是守灵 瞧你在这里走来走去 鸡巴梆硬的样子
You're walking around the wake with a fucking hard-on.
我没有 我...
I'm not. I'm...
我只是建议 由我来出面
All I am suggesting is that I swing it for us,
然后我们三个继续推进
and then we move ahead, us three
皮尔斯 泛美网科 所有
Pierce, ATN, everything.
好 很好 非常好
Okay, good. Great.
我有一些想法
Well, I have some thoughts
我想我也有一些想法
Yeah. I guess I have some thoughts too
你不会是想支持格丽吧
You're not pulling for Gerr-bear?
什么 我吗 当然不会 我...我不想
What, me? Hell no. No, I'm... I'm done
再帮老太太过马路了
helping old ladies cross the street
但 我确实有疑问
But I do wonder about...
对我有疑问 对吧  -对
About me? Yeah.   -Yeah.
好吧  -我觉得 应该由我出面
Okay.   -I think it needs to be me too.
是吗 好吧
Uh  -huh. Okay.
是的 我们...
Yeah. We're doing what we do.
齐心协力  -好吧
together.   -Well,
这就是我的最终目的
ultimately, that's how I want it
兄弟 别这样 他不过是在纸上
Man, come on. You're jerking over a piece of paper
写了你的名字 别兴奋过头了
that he scribbled your fucking name on.
江湖传言 你在两个世界中都是最糟糕的
There is an argument that you're the worst of both worlds
不同的场景 相同的结果
Different, but the same.
但这招 对董事会管用 小西 真的管用
That plays, Shiv, it does, with the board
换汤不换药
Same old but with a vibey new banner
根据计划草案 我是首席运营官对吧
COO is on the draft plan, right? Like,
对吧  -对
right?   -Yeah.
我是首席运营官
I'm the COO.
我认识马特森 我和爸关系密切
And I know Matsson. And I was very close with Dad
我们的一部分沟通内容
We had a number of communications
你们是知道的 但说实话
that you were aware of and some that, honestly
虽然现在说这些不太合时宜 但也有一些内容你们不了解
now's not the time, but you were not.
是的 我们关系不错 而且说实话 肯
And yeah, I just think we were close and honestly, Ken
这样不太好 对吧
it doesn't feel good, right?
你独占一切
For it to be just... you
是的
Yeah.
所以 这就是我的想法
So, them's my words.
好吧
Uh  -huh.
我明白了
I see that.
是的 我明白了 兄弟
Yeah. I see that, bro.
是吗  -是的
You do?   -Yeah.
小罗 不一定非得由我一个人出面
I mean, Rome, it doesn't have to be just me.
我同意 你说得有道理
I'm down. It makes sense.
好的吧
M'kay.
那我呢
And what about me?
老实说 我担心
Honestly, I just worry...
自己看起来像是在强词夺理
it looks like special pleading
首席运营官的人选
Like, it's the COO's.
在计划草案中已经明确了
It's in the draft plan
而纸上写的是我的名字
I'm on the piece of paper
那个人必须看起来情绪稳定
It... It needs to look fucking dry
干净利落 坚韧不拔
and clean and tough
我不是吗
And I don't?
不是吗 我看起来睡眼惺忪 蓬头垢面
Yeah? I look too teary eyed and mascara streaked,
分分钟都有可能晕倒 是吗
and like I might fucking faint?
我够干净利落了吧  -小西 这不是
It's clean enough.   -Shiv, it's not... it's not...
我觉得这行不通
really... I don't think it works
你确实没有经验
You actually don't have experience.
理由站不住脚
It starts to look flaky.
战略审查是我做的
I did the strategic review.
那是爸给你铺的路
That was "Daddy make work."
而且“两个和尚抬水喝 三个和尚.
And besides, I think two is cool but three is...
三个和尚…  -三个和尚没水喝
Like, three is...   -Three is a bit wonky
我是说 两个人是正经性爱.
I mean, two is... fucking
三个人就是嬉皮士的纵欲狂欢了
and three is like some weird orgy for hippies.
我不认为董事会能同意三个人
I can't see the board going for three.
我必须分到一杯
Well, I need to wet my beak
只是由我们两个出面而已
We'd only be fronting it.
我不需要刷脸 也不是自尊心作祟
I don't need to be front facing, and it's not about ego.
当然 我们是三人团队
Really, it's the three bie. It's the team.
是啊 事事都有你的份
Yeah, you're inside everything.
可以吗 就像...我没想伤害任何人 好吧
Okay? This is like... I'm not trying to fuck anyone, okay?
只是为了说服董事会 昨天...
This is just to sell, and yesterday was...
别这样 天...很真实
Come on. Like, yesterday was fucking... That was real
我想我们...
And I think we're...
我感觉很好...我觉得没有问题
I feel really good about this. This is... I think this is good
我需要了解一切  -一切可以…
I need to be across everything.   -Everything. Yeah
只是缓兵之计
Yeah. It's a holding position.
暂时的
It's holding.
我们会完成交易 把泛美网科运作起来 让皮尔斯加入
We'll do the deal. Spin ATN, fold in Pierce.
可能六个月 可能八个月  -利益均分吗
Six months, eight months.   -And that's all equal?
是的  -必须均分 分毫不差
-Yeah.   -Equal as fuck, to the gram.
因为 如果你们给我设了套 而且...
Cause you guys fuck me on this, and it'...
没有
No.
那你们以爸的名义保证
This is a Dad promise. On yesterday
行  -以昨天的名义
Yeah.   -On yesterday
以昨天的名义
On yesterday
不会搞你的
Not gonna fuck you.
你们想谈谈吗
You guys wanna talk?
准备好了吗  -是的
Ready?   -Yeah.
好
Okay
可以了吗
Okay?
可以吗
Yeah?
我想在董事会正式开始前
I think, uh, pre-board,
我们希望先内部沟通
we were just hoping it would be just us.
不 参会人员没问题
Oh, no. This is a good group
我不确定这样讨论是否合适
I'm just not sure it's appropriate for this discussion
如果你不接受 弗兰克 你可以滚
Well, if you're uncomfortable, Frank, you can fuck off.
一群可爱的朋友在聊天而已 对吧
This is a lovely gang of pals having a chat. Okay?
听着 很简单
Look, it's simple.
应急计划草案中 确定了首席运营官人选
CoOs are on the draft emergency plan.
如果不遵从的话 会显得很不正常
It looks perverse not to honor that
而且 显得故意针对我们
and it looks pointed for it not to be us.
我和罗曼上台
Me and Roman step up
那么
Well, uh,
你们最后一次跟你们老爸说话 是什么时候
when was the last time you spoke with your dad?
大概48小时以前吧  -你们聊得怎么样
Like, 48 hours ago.   -And how'd that go?
还不错  -是吗
It went well.   -Well?
肯 司法部那边已经有了结论
Ken, the DOJ's all wrapped up
你发表的关于洛根的一切言论都毫无用处
and everything you said about Logan amounted to nothing.
你已经臭了
You're damaged goods
而我却 切实带来了一些 企业文化上的转向
Whereas I shepherded in, um, a lot of cultural change.
我想我们大家都知道 老爸对格丽很有意见
I think we all know that Dad had soured on Gerri
我可不觉得有什么书面记录 能证实这个说法
I don't think there's anything on paper to that effect
但我也没想争这个
But I'm not gonna push it.
我们显然就该是父亲的接班人
We're obviously the people to take over for Dad
我们是他最亲近的人
We were closest to him.
我想董事会可能会有点想法
I think the board could have concerns
这个嘛 肯德你的名字就在那张纸上
Well, Kendall's name is on a piece of paper
洛根也说过 这个位置该是他的
Logan said it should be Kendall
这是什么时候的事呢  -很多次呢
But when?   -A few times.
你们已经失去了洛根
You've lost Logan.
他虽然也有过错 但毕竟公司是他建立起来的
And for his faults, he was the founder.
肯和罗曼
Ken and Roman
我觉得罗伊科有个罗伊挺好的
I think a Roy at Royco works
再说 这只是临时的
It's not for long.
这样 你就能把他们变成你的傀儡
So you can puppet master them.
谁 我吗 弗兰克  -闭嘴吧
Who? Me, Frank?   -Get the fuck outta here.
别说了
Come on.
和马特森的谈判会重新启动
There will be the renegotiation with Matsson.
我只想完成交易 功成身退 我们都有自己的想法
I wanna do the deal and get out. We've got our own ideas
泛美网科获得新生 其他事情也就可以开始推进了
With ATN refreshed, there's a shape for things
我们有正在孵化中的想法  -对
For us, we have things cooking.   -Yeah
这么说吧 我们知道董事会非常中意这桩交易
I mean, we... we know that the board is very excited
我们也是 这笔交易相当诱人
about the deal. So are we, it's a good deal
是个好买卖  -对
It is a good deal.   -Yeah.
历史正在发生
History is happening.
你嗅到那种气息了吗  -当然
Can you smell it?   -Sure
玫瑰和尸体的腐臭
Roses and the rotting corpses.
好的 好的 结束了
Okay. Okay, it's done.
尘埃落定 他们投票决定了
It's done. They voted it through
肯和罗曼吗  -肯和罗曼从COO升级接班掌门人
Ken and Rome?   -Ken and Rome step up from COO
起草文件吧 雨果 快
Let's draft it, Hugo, right now.
肯和罗曼 好的  -我去答复...
Ken and Rome. All right!   -And I'll reply to...
吾王万岁
Long live the king!
还有另一个王也是
And the other king.
你好
Hi.
事情还顺利吧  -当然了 非常顺利
Everything well?   -Yeah. All great. All good
那就好
Great.
还笑呢 闭嘴 别笑了
Yeah. Shut the fuck up
不准笑 又不是脱口秀大会
and stop laughing. It's not a comedy night
我靠
God. Ow! Ooh, shoot
亲爱的  -不用 我没事
Hey. Hey, honey.   -No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
我没事 我很好
I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
别他妈碰我
Don't fucking touch me.
能别... 能别笑了吗
Stop... stop smiling!
谁也不准进来
No one comes in here
现在你要接管公司了
So, you're running the company
恭喜啊
Congratulations
是啊 谢谢你 美好的一天 美好的一周
Yeah, yeah. Thankyou. Great day. Great week
你知道他还做数独吗
Did you know he did Sudoku?
好像是吧
Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
他好像是会玩数独 我有点印象
he did them. I... I think I... I think I knew that
我的天哪
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ
你们没事吧  -没事
You guys okay?   -Yeah.
真的吗  -没事的
Yeah?   -Yeah, yeah, yeah
对  -好吧 抱歉这时候打扰你们
Yeah.   -Okay, yeah. I'm sorry that we have to...
但是我们必须得拟好声明
you know. But we are putting together the statement
宣布你和…
announcing you and…
我们会和你们的人 对个人简历的细节严格把关
we'll go through all the biographical details
就是想跟宣传和公关这边
with your offices, and yeah, just wanted to check in
对好一些事情
on Comms and PR.
还有很多困难的决定 需要拍板...
And there's also a lot of guite difficult decisions, so...
对 我们想说的
Yes. I guess what we wanted to say
是一些媒体方面的事情
from a Comms point of view,
注意 这只是出于新闻传播考虑
and listen, this is strictly Comms, but the markets
周一就要开市了
are gonna open on Monday
有很多个法子可以让你们
And, um, there are a number of ways
把这个位子坐得更稳当 明白吗
to solidify your guys' position. Okay?
洛根还在的时候
When Logan was with us
我们竭尽全力提升他的声望
we did everything we could to burnish his reputation
现在 你们接了他的班 所以我们也会竭尽全力
Now, you're taking over so we wanna do everything we can
提升你们的声望
to burnish your reputations
我们有两条路子可以走
Yeah. I guess there are two ways to go
要么
They're sort of.
走洛根永垂不朽的路子
Operation Embalm Lenin
不然就是另外的思路
or there's another way
如果走第一条路
Yeah, for the first option, we, you know.
我们可以找一些你们和父亲一家人其乐融融的合照
just put together a nice package of photos with you and your dad.
表示公司在你们手上安全无虞 再提一提那张纸
You're a safe pair of hands, mention the piece of paper
你们会严格按照洛根的遗志经营公司 萧规曹随
And you're gonna follow what Logan Roy did to the letter.
另一条路的话 就要复杂一点 侧重于破旧立新
Or there's a more complex, more fresh start
接着说  -我再次声明
Go on.   -And this is, again
这只是公关手段 没有别的意思
just a PR perspective, yeah?
外界会有对你们的能力的质疑
There's gonna be an issue about your competence
所以 打个比方 我们或许可以强调一下
And so, maybe, if we stress, for example
你们此前 对于公司事务 就已经有很深的参与度了
how involved you've already been previously
说得再过一点 我们可以说 在他临终之前
So, toughest version, we say that he was.
他已经慢慢地失去掌控力了
losing his focus towards the end
懂了 这是"洛根是老糊涂“计划
Okay. So, it's Operation Shit-On-Dad
不是
No.
就是这样  -不
Yeah. Yes, it is.   -No
我觉得那张纸就足够服众了
I think the piece of paper is strong
好的  -好吧
Okay.   -Okay.
你真的觉得人们会相信
You really think that people are gonna buy that
老爸是傀儡皇帝这种说辞吗
Dad was a fucking puppet?
这只是一个备选方案而已 罗曼
It's just an option, Roman.
洛根·罗伊是一个伟大的人
Logan Roy was a great man.
然而 近来他身边的人
However, lately, the people around him
在代替他决策
have been making the big decisions
他的孩子们是幕后的决策者
His kids have been pulling the strings
我的意思是 我们可以按你们的接受程度调整说辞
I mean, we can go as far as you like.
我个人不会这么做 但是公事公论
I wouldn't, but it is our job
我们可以写一写康纳的妈妈
to say that we could go to Connor's mom.
她遭受的身体和语言暴力 还有凯莉的事情
Physical and verbal abuse. The Kerry situation
好了好了 不要再提这些了 好吗
Okay. Well. That's... All right. Okay? Yeah, I... I... !
我感觉
I do have, uh.
有一点点恶心
certain feelings of queasiness about, I guess
他现在尸骨未寒 我们就开始编排他
shitting on our dad while he's still up at Frank E. Campbell's
是的 现在这个时间
Yeah. Right now, I would say
考虑到我们的父亲刚刚去世
considering our dad has just died
或许我们确实不应该诋毁他
we should maybe not shit on Dad
对 谢谢 卡洛丽娜
Yeah. Thanks, Karolina.
也谢谢你了 老混蛋 但是
You too, fuckface. But...
请不要在我们面前 提这么下作的事情了
maybe don't bring us this disgusting shit ever again
好吗  -好的
Okay?   -Sure.
不管怎么说 还是谢谢你  -我理解 我理解
Thanks, anyway.   -Understood. Understood
抱歉 谢谢你 罗曼  -谢了 雨果
Sorry. Thanks, Roman.   -Thanks, Hugo
对不起
Yep.Apologies
那什么 雨果
Hey, Hugo.
关于那个事情
You know the stuff?
什么
What stuff?
爆老爸黑料这事
The bad Dad stuff.
知道 怎么了
Uh  -huh. Yeah.
如果是他 他会这么做的 为了公司 他会这么做的
It's what he would do. He'd want this for the firm.
是啊
Right. Okay.
去做吧 别说得太绝 别留什么痕迹
So, action that. But soft, no prints.
好 但是 我不想
Right. I mean, I don't wanna.
我有点担心自由行动会出问题
I'm a little concerned of freelance.
我可以去征求卡洛丽娜和罗曼的同意吗
Can I get a sign off from Karolina and Roman?
不行 低调
No, pal. No. Down-low.
去做就好了
Just get on it.
还是说 你想谈谈你那个内线交易的事?
Unless you want me to pull out the strap-on.